<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Open Privacy Vault on</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content in Open Privacy Vault on</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-US</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 06 Oct 2020 08:47:36 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>1. Introduction</title><link>/docs/overview/introduction/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/overview/introduction/</guid><description>Open Privacy Vault - Secure, Performant, Open Source PII as a Service.
Quick Start Running Local OPV Start from source code:
git clone https://github.com/open-privacy/opv cd opv make vendor make run Start from docker image. You may need to start control plane and data plane separatedly.
docker run -it -v /tmp/opv_data:/data -p 28000:28000 openprivacyio/opv dataplane docker run -it -v /tmp/opv_data:/data -p 27999:27999 openprivacyio/opv controlplane APIs For more information, please take a look at</description></item><item><title>Data Plane API</title><link>/docs/development/dataplane_api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/dataplane_api/</guid><description/></item><item><title>2. Architecture</title><link>/docs/overview/architecture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/overview/architecture/</guid><description>Network Components Data Models</description></item><item><title>Control Plane API</title><link>/docs/development/controlplane_api/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/controlplane_api/</guid><description>TODO</description></item><item><title>3. Planes</title><link>/docs/overview/planes/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/overview/planes/</guid><description>Planes are separated entrypoints and ports to access different segments of OPV. Currently OPV is planning to support the following planes:
Control Plane Data Plane Proxy Plane (TODO) Control Plane Control plane (default port: 27999) is a group of controllers that handle the admin related logic. In your network, you should do your best to isolate the access to the control plane.
👉 Please don't expose control plane to the public network.</description></item><item><title>Playground</title><link>/docs/development/playground/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/playground/</guid><description>PII Tokenization Demo Testing via the Data Plane of https://playground.openprivacy.io.
Checkr API Proxy Demo TODO</description></item><item><title>4. Env Configuration</title><link>/docs/overview/env/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/overview/env/</guid><description>OPV&amp;rsquo;s configuration is currently done via environment variables. Please follow the source code and comments.
env.go</description></item><item><title>Source Code</title><link>/docs/development/source/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/source/</guid><description>Development related commands can be found in the Makefile file.
Compile from the source Make sure you have go, make, docker, and docker-compose installed.
# Prepare dependencies and compile opv make vendor make run One can open the local swagger UI to test the APIs:
Default DataPlane Swagger URL: http://127.0.0.1:28000/swagger/index.html Default ControlPlane Swagger URL: http://127.0.0.1:27999/swagger/index.html Generate swagger 2.0 When you make any change to APIs (e.g. pkg/dataplane, pkg/controlplane, pkg/apimodel), you may want to regenerate the swagger 2.</description></item><item><title>5. Encryption</title><link>/docs/overview/encryption/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/overview/encryption/</guid><description>Supported Encryption Engine OPV&amp;rsquo;s encryption is designed to work with multiple encryption engines. Currently supported encryption engines are
NaCl Secretbox Hashicorp Vault (TODO) Transit Secret Built-in secretbox encryption engine Secretbox uses XSalsa20 and Poly1305 to encrypt and authenticate messages with secret-key cryptography.
For example, to configure the built-in secretbox encryption engine, you can set a list of secret keys to use. The first key is always the secret key for encryption, and all the keys will be used for decryption, which allows key rotation.</description></item><item><title>FAQ</title><link>/docs/development/faq/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/development/faq/</guid><description>How to migrate database? By default, OPV uses ent for auto migration. If the OPV_DB_DRIVER and OPV_DB_CONNECTION_STR is set corrently with the right database permission, OPV will run the database migration on startup (including both dataplane and controlplane).</description></item></channel></rss>